(Penny:)Hey, guys. Sorry you had to wait,
but we are swamped.
(Penny:)What's this?
(Leonard:)Sheldon took our order.
(Penny:)Sheldon doesn't work here.
(Leonard:)Well, honey, not to complain...
(Leonard:)...but we were starting to think
you didn't either.
[DISHES SHATTER]
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)Is that really necessary?
(Sheldon:)Good Lord.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)The interference pattern
in the fracture.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)The motion of the wave
through the structure.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)I've been looking at it all wrong.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)I can't consider
the electrons as particles.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)They move through the graphene
as a wave.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)It's a wave!
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)The moment to applaud would be now.
(Sheldon(drops tray. A nearby table claps):)Troglodytes.
(Penny:)Sheldon. Where are you going?
Aren't you gonna clean this?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I don't work here.